

Aakarsha n Thapa

Web Developer | Full Stack, Web Technologies | Database Technologies

CONTACT

- 14374996061
- akarsan.thapa@gmail.com
- 7242 Wainbrook Road , Mississauga, ON
- github.com/akarsanth
- witter.com/ThapaAkarsan https://www.linkedin.com/in
- in /aakarshan-thapa-28889a11b/

SKILLS

- Database Systems: Oracle
 Database, MySQL
- Software Applications: Microsoft word, Excel, Spreadsheet
- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- React | Next JS | Node js
- Excellent Communication skills

LANGUAGE

English

Nepali

SUMMARY

Enthusiastic web developer here, good with React, Next.js, Node.js, Express, SQL, and MongoDB. Always up for learning new tech stuff. I'm great at solving tricky problems and turning them into neat solutions. I can handle both front-end and back-end work, making me a useful team player in any project phase. Experience with Microsoft office tools such as Word and Excel.

EDUCATION

Bsc (Hons) Computing

Informatics College Pokhara (London Metropolitan University) / Pokhara / November, 2019 - November, 2022 <u>Graduated with First Class Honours</u> (Grade A)

Full Stack Software Development (Post Graduate)

Lambton College / Mississauga / January, 2024 - Present

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Internship

E.K. Solutions Pvt. Ltd. / Kathmandu, Nepal / August, 2022 - November, 2022

- Learned about different tools/libraries such as Formik, Redux, React Router, and Next JS which aid in React Frontend development.
- Acquired essential knowledge such as Git/Github, QA, SDLC, API, and Postman.

Web Application Developer

Arambha IT / Pokhara, Nepal / January, 2023 - April, 2023

- Excelled as a React developer: Designed user experiences and crafted interfaces beyond coding.
- Developed not just technical skills but excelled as a problemsolver aligning with company culture and project goals.

PROJECTS INVOLVED

eCommerce Web Application

Developed an eCommerce Web Application as a Final Year Project. Technologies used such as React JS, Material UI, Express JS, Redux Toolkit (for state management), MySQL, and other libraries such as Formik, Yup, and Sequelize ORM.

https://github.com/akarsanth/omnifurni

Grocery Store Web Application

Web application developed as a final project during the internship period in Ekbana Solutions.

https://github.com/akarsanth/grocery_store_fp